Register of the American Relief Administration Russian operational records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Moscow Office, Correspondence File, 1921-1923
  - Novorossisk (Box 194)
    - Telegrams
      - Moscow
        - From (Box 196, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 255
  - Novorossisk Port
    - Corn exchange (Folder 2)
    - History (Folder 3)
    - Letters
      - To London, (1-39) (Folder 4)
      - From London (1-29) (Folder 5)
    - Pilot Station (Folder 6)
    - Reports (Folder 7)
      Available on microfilm reel 256
    - Telegrams
      - Constantinople
        - To (Folder 8)
        - From (Folder 9)
      - London
        - To (Folder 10)
        - From (Folder 11)
  - Odessa. Letters to Moscow (Box 197)
    - (1-200), 1921 December 11-1922 April 11 (Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 257
    - (201-368), 1922 April 11 -May 27 (Folder 2)
    - (369-550), 1922 May 27 -July 19 (Box 198, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 258
    - (551-1000), 1922 July 20 -August 15 (Folder 2)
    - (1-160), 1922 October 12-31 (Box 199, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 259
    - (161-627), 1922 November 1 -December 26 (Folder 2)
    - (627-1000), 1923 January 2 -February 27 (Box 200, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 260
    - (1-499), 1923 February 21 -May 15 (Folder 2)
      Available on microfilm reel 261
    - (500-679), 1923 May 16 -June 25 (Box 201, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 262
  - Odessa Port
    - Letters
      - To Moscow
        - 1922 February -April (1-17) (Folder 2)
        - (1-253), 1922 February 20-1923 January 18 (Folder 3)
        - (254-518), 1923 January 20 -June 26 (Box 202, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 263
      - From Moscow
        - (1-200), 1921 November 10-1922 April 14 (Folder 2)
        - (1-763), 1921 December 2-1923 June 20 (Box 203, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 264
        - (46-225), 1922 November 2-1923 May 14 (Folder 2)
          Available on microfilm reel 265
    - Medical statistics and reports to Moscow, 1922 January 24 -September 21 (Folder 3)
  - Orenburg (Box 204)
    - Letters to Moscow
      - (200-450), 1922 April 18 -July 27 (Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 266
      - (451-738), 1922 July 27 -October 2 (Folder 2)
      - (1-277), 1923 January 30 -June 26 (Box 205, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 267
    - Medical statistics and reports from Moscow
      - 1921 November 10-1922 September 30 (Folder 2)
      - (1-75), 1922 December 8-1923 June 7 (Folder 3)
  - Paris. Letters (Box 206)
    - To Moscow, (5-37), 1923 January 8 -May 14 (Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 268
    - From Moscow, (1-85), 1922 December 11-1923 July 9 (Folder 2)
  - Petrograd. Letters
    - To Moscow
      - (1-360), 1921 September 11-1922 February 18 (Folder 3)
      - (361-665), 1922 February 18 -March 4 (Box 207, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 269
      - (666-950), 1922 May 6 -June 26 (Box 208, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 270
      - (951-1285), 1922 June 23 -August 24 (Box 209, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 270A
      - (1286-1588), 1922 August 26 -October 31 (Box 210, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 271
      - (1589-1872), 1922 October 31-1923 March 30 (Folder 2)
      - (1873-2099), 1923 April 2 -June 19 (Box 211, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 272
      - (1-112), 1922 November 11 -December 29 (Folder 2)
      - (166-395), 1923 February 1 -June 18 (Folder 3)
    - From Moscow (Box 212)
      - (1-799), 1921 September 6-1922 March 30 (Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 273
      - (800-897), 1922 April 2 -June 16 (Folder 2)
      - (1-67), 1922 July 5 -October 30 (Folder 3)
  - Petrograd Port (Box 213)
    - Letters
      - To Moscow
        - (1-448). Includes telegrams, 1922 July 18 -October 30 (Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 274
        - (814-1076), 1923 January 2 -March 13 (Box 214, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 275
      - From Moscow
        - (449-813), 1922 October 31 -December 29 (Folder 2)
        - (68-217), 1922 November 2-1923 March 15 (Folder 3)
    - Medical statistics and reports to and from Moscow, 1921 September 22-1922 February 7 (Box 215, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 276
  - Ribinsk. Letters (Box 216)
    - To Moscow, (1-108), 1922 March 18 -August 13 (Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 277
    - From Moscow, (1-58), 1922 March 27 -August 9 (Folder 2)
  - Riga. Letters
    - To Moscow
      - (390-633), 1922 January 16 -March 31 (Folder 3)
      - (634-863), 1922 April 1 -May 27 (Box 217, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 278
      - (864-1000), 1922 May 29 -July 18 (Folder 2)
      - (1-338), 1922 August 21-1923 July 13 (Box 218, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 279
      - (318-701), 1923 January 2 -July 13 (Folder 2)
    - From Moscow (Box 219)
      - (1-880), 1921 November 27-1923 July 12 (Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 280
      - (1-554), 1922 September 1 -November 2 (Box 220, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 281
  - Rostov
    - Letters
      - To Moscow
        - (1-196), 1922 January 28 -June 13 (Folder 2)
        - (197-454), 1922 June 14 -October 31 (Box 221, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 282
        - (455-870), 1922 November 3-1923 March 31 (Folder 2)
        - (871-1133), 1923 April 23 -June 23 (Box 222, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 283
      - From Moscow
        - (1-119), 1922 January 13 -September 28 (Folder 2)
        - (1-369) [to Tsaritsyn], 1922 January 13 -June 15 (Folder 3)
    - Medical statistics and reports (Box 223, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 284
  - Samara
    - Letters
      - To Moscow
        - (1-250), 1921 September 27-1922 March 24 (Folder 2)
        - (251-500), 1922 March 24 -July 15 (Box 224, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 285
        - (501-779), 1922 July 15 -September 30 (Folder 2)
        - (780-1132), 1922 October 2 -December 30 (Box 225, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 286
        - (1134-1517), 1923 January 2 -March 31 (Box 226, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 287
        - (1518-1857), 1923 March 31 -June 30 (Box 227, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 288
      - From Moscow, (1-643), 1921 September 21-1923 May 14 (Folder 2)
    - Medical statistics and reports to and from Moscow, 1921 October 31-1923 May 9 (Box 228, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 289
  - Saratov
    - Letters
      - General
        - To Moscow
          - (1-130), 1921 October 26-1922 January 7 (Folder 2)
          - (131-203), 1922 January 7 -March 4 (Folder 3)
          - (204-300), 1922 March 4 -May 5 (Box 229, Folder 1)
            Available on microfilm reel 290
          - (301-405), 1922 May 5 -July 3 (Folder 2)
          - (406-501), 1922 July 3 -August 16 (Folder 3)
          - (502-616), 1922 August 16 -September 30 (Folder 4)
          - (617-705), 1922 October 2 -November 8 (Box 230, Folder 1)
            Available on microfilm reel 291
          - (706-790), 1922 November 8 -December 13 (Folder 2)
          - (791-901), 1922 December 18-1923 January 31 (Folder 3)
          - (902-973), 1923 January 31 -February 28 (Folder 4)
          - (977-1097), 1923 March 3 -April 30 (Box 231, Folder 1)
            Available on microfilm reel 292
          - (1098-1219), 1923 May 2 -June 23 (Folder 2)
        - From Moscow, (1-671), 1921 October 1-1923 June 20 (Folder 3)
      - Food Remittance Division (Box 232)
        - To Moscow
          - (1-500), 1922 March 28 -October 4 (Folder 1)
            Available on microfilm reel 293
          - (501-1053), 1922 October 4-1923 May 11 (Box 233, Folder 1)
            Available on microfilm reel 294
        - From Moscow
          - (1054-1191), 1923 May 11 -June 15 (Folder 2)
    - Medical statistics and reports to Moscow, 1922 December 18-1923 May 15 (Box 234, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 295
  - Simbirsk (Box 235)
    - Letters
      - To Moscow
        - (1-258), 1921 October 13-1922 April 12 (Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 296
        - (286-500), 1922 April 13 -June 9 (Folder 2)
        - (501-912), 1922 June 8 -September 30 (Box 236, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 297
        - (913-1190), 1922 October 2 -December 31 (Box 237, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 298
        - (1191-1451), 1923 January 2 -March 31 (Folder 2)
        - (1452-1692), 1923 April 2 -June 21 (Box 238, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 299
      - From Moscow, (1-478), 1921 October 1-1923 June 20 (Folder 2)
    - Medical statistics and reports to Moscow, 1921 November 9-1923 May 19 (Box 239, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 300
  - Tsaritsyn (Box 240)
    - Letters
      - To Moscow
        - (1-366), 1921 November 13-1922 September 29 (Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 301
        - (367-524), 1922 October 1 -November 30 (Folder 2)
      - To and from Moscow, (1-290), 1921 October 20-1922 November 23 (Box 241, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 302
    - Medical statistics and reports, 1921 October 20 -December 21 (Folder 2)
  - Ufa
    - Letters
      - To Moscow
        - (1-200), 1921 November 10-1922 March 31 (Folder 3)
        - (297-565), 1922 June 9 -October 31 (Box 242, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 303
        - (566-769), 1922 November 1-1923 January 28 (Box 243, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 304
        - (770-1122), 1923 February 3 -July 1 (Folder 2)
      - From Moscow (Box 244)
        - (1-371), 1921 November 2-1923 January 31 (Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 305
        - (394-496), 1923 March 3 -June 28 (Folder 2)
    - Medical statistics and reports to and from Moscow, 1921 December-1923 May 12 (Folder 3)
  - Ukraine (Box 245)
    - Letters
      - To Moscow, (1-372), 1922 April 21 -October 23 (Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 306
      - From Moscow, (1-226), 1922 May 26 -October 4 (Box 246, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 307
    - Medical statistics and reports (Folder 2)
  - Vienna. Letters
    - To Moscow, (1-38), 1922 December 15-1923 April 19 (Folder 3)
    - From Moscow, (1-6, 10-11), 1922 December 15-1923 June 5 (Folder 4)
  - Vitebsk. Letters
    - To Moscow
      - (1-250), 1922 January 19 -June 26 (Folder 5)
      - (251-619), 1922 June 26 -December 30 (Box 247, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 308
      - (620-951), 1923 January 2 -June 29 (Box 248, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 309
    - From Moscow, (1-321), 1923 January 3 -June 19 (Folder 2)
  - Warsaw. Letters (Box 249)
    - To Moscow, (1-312), 1921 December 1-1923 June 1 (Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 310
    - From Moscow, (1-184), 1921 December 1-1923 July 16 (Folder 2)
- Moscow Office, Telegrams, 1921-1923
  Telegrams sent and received by the Moscow office, arranged alphabetically by geographic area (primarily cities).
  - Akchurino - District of Columbia, to and from Moscow (Box 250, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 311
  - Ekaterniburg, to Moscow (Folder 2)
  - Ekaterinolar, to Moscow (Folder 3)
  - Ekaterinoslav, to and from Moscow (Folder 4)
    Available on microfilm reel 312
  - Elizavetgrag, to and from Moscow (Box 251, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 313
  - Essentuki, to Moscow (Folder 2)
  - Eupatoria, to and from Moscow (Folder 3)
  - Faustovo, to Moscow (Folder 4)
  - Feodosia, to and from Moscow (Folder 5)
  - Florence, to Moscow (Folder 6)
    Available on microfilm reel 314
  - Glazunovka, to Moscow (Folder 7)
  - Gomel, to and from Moscow (Folder 8)
  - Gorodishche, to Moscow (Folder 9)
  - Gravenhage, to Moscow (Folder 10)
  - Grigoriopol, to Moscow (Folder 11)
  - Gzhel, to Moscow (Folder 12)
  - Hague, The, to Moscow (Folder 13)
  - Hamburg, to and from Moscow (Folder 14)
  - Harbin, to Moscow (Folder 15)
  - Hartford, to Moscow (Folder 16)
  - Haverhill, to Moscow (Folder 17)
  - Helsingfors (Helsinki), to Moscow (Folder 18)
  - Iaroslavl, to Moscow (Folder 19)
  - Inza, to Moscow (Folder 20)
  - Ivanovo, from Moscow (Folder 21)
  - Kaluga, to Moscow (Folder 22)
  - Kanadeia, to Moscow (Folder 23)
  - Karnovka, to Moscow (Folder 24)
  - Karsun, to Moscow (Folder 25)
  - Kazan (Box 252)
    - To and from Moscow
      - (1-1000), 1921 September 20-1922 November 9 (Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 315
      - (1-177), 1922 November 10-1923 July 9 (Folder 2)
    - From Moscow
      - (1-1000), 1921 September 12-1923 June 25 (Folder 3)
        Available on microfilm reel 316
      - (1-4), 1923 June 29 -July 9 (Folder 4)
  - Kharkov, to Moscow (Box 253, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 317
  - Kharkov, Kherson, to and from Moscow (Folder 2)
  - Kiev, to Moscow (Folder 3)
    Available on microfilm reel 318
  - Kiev, Kluchiki, Kobe, to and from Moscow (Box 254, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 319
  - Koslov, to and from Moscow (Folder 2)
    Available on microfilm reel 320
  - Latvia - Lodz, to and from Moscow (Folder 3)
  - London (Box 255)
    - To Moscow
      - (Black 1-1000), 1921 August 31-1922 February 21 (Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 321
      - (Black 1-1000), 1922 February 21 -May 16 (Folder 2)
        Available on microfilm reel 321A
      - (Black 1-1000), 1922 May 16 -August 12 (Box 256, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 322
      - (Black 1-1000), 1922 August 12-1923 March 10 (Folder 2)
        Available on microfilm reel 322A
      - (Black 1-157), 1923 March 10 -July 18 (Folder 3)
    - From Moscow (Box 257)
      - (Black 1-1080), 1921 August 28-1922 February 18 (Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 323
      - (1-500), 1922 February 18 -March 16 (Folder 2)
        Available on microfilm reel 324
      - (501-999), 1922 March 16 -April (Box 258, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 325
      - (1-999), 1922 April 20 -June 23 (Folder 2)
        Available on microfilm reel 326
      - (1-999), 1922 June 19 -September 18 (Box 259, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 327
      - (1-577), 1922 September 18 -November 10 (Folder 2)
        Available on microfilm reel 328
  - Minsk
    - To Moscow (Folder 3)
    - From Moscow (Box 260, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 329
  - New York, to Moscow (Folder 2)
  - Nikolaev, to and from Moscow (Folder 3)
  - Nizhnii Novgorod, to and from Moscow (Folder 4)
  - Odessa
    - To Moscow (Folder 5)
      Available on microfilm reel 330
    - To Moscow (Box 261, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 331
    - From Moscow (Folder 2)
      Available on microfilm reel 332
    - From Moscow (Box 262, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 333
  - Orel, to Moscow (Folder 2)
  - Orenburg
    - To Moscow (Folder 3)
    - From Moscow (Folder 4)
      Available on microfilm reel 334
  - Petrograd (Box 263)
    - To and from Moscow (Folder 1)
    - To Moscow (Folder 2-4)
      Available on microfilm reels 335-337
    - From Moscow (Box 264, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 338
  - Riga
    - To Moscow (Folder 2)
      Available on microfilm reel 339
    - To Moscow (Box 265, Folder 1-3)
      Available on microfilm reels 340 and 341
    - From Moscow (Box 266, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 341
  - Rome to Moscow (Folder 2)
    Available on microfilm reel 342
  - Rostov, to and from Moscow (Box 267, Folder 1-2)
    Available on microfilm reels 342 and 343
  - Samara
    - To Moscow (Folder 3)
      Available on microfilm reel 343
    - To Moscow (Box 268, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 344
    - From Moscow (Folder 2)
      Available on microfilm reel 345
  - Saransk, Tsaritsyn, to and from Moscow (Box 269, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 345A
  - Saratov
    - To Moscow (Folder 2)
      Available on microfilm reel 346
    - From Moscow (Folder 3)
      Available on microfilm reel 346A
  - Simbirsk (Box 270)
    - To Moscow (Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 347
    - From Moscow (Folder 2)
      Available on microfilm reel 347A
  - Simferopol, to and from Moscow (Folder 3)
  - Trenton, Wiesbaden, to and from Moscow (Box 271, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 348
  - Ufa
    - To Moscow (Folder 2)
    - From Moscow (Box 272, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 349
  - Ukraine, Visoky, to and from Moscow (Folder 2)
  - Vienna, to and from Moscow (Folder 3)
    Available on microfilm reel 349A
  - Vitebsk
    - To Moscow (Folder 4)
    - From Moscow (Folder 5)
  - Voronezh, to and from Moscow (Box 273, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 350
  - Warsaw
    - To Moscow (Folder 2)
    - From Moscow (Folder 3)
  - Washington, to Moscow (Folder 4)
  - Winchester, to Moscow (Folder 5)
  - Windau, to Moscow (Folder 6)
  - Zaporozie (Folder 7)
  - Zhitomir, to Moscow (Folder 8)
  - Zmieve (Folder 9)
- Moscow Office, Chronological File of Letters Sent, 1921-1923
  Available on microfilm reels 351-356
  Miscellaneous letters sent by the Moscow office, arranged chronologically.
  - (1-700), 1921 September 2-1922 March 10 (Box 274, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 351
  - (701-1402), 1922 March 10 -June 30 (Box 275, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 352
  - (1403-2200), 1922 June 30 -September 18 (Box 276, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 353
  - (2324-3576), 1922 October 2 -December 27 (Box 277, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 354
  - (3577-4274), 1923 January 3 -March 31 (Box 278, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 355
  - (4275-4635), 1923 April 2 -May 15 (Box 279, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 356
  - (4636-5137), 1923 May 16 -July 19 (Folder 2)
- Moscow Office, Soviet Government Correspondence, 1921-1923
  Available on microfilm reels 357-378
  Correspondence between the Soviet government and the Moscow office of the A.R.A., arranged by subseries (letters received and letters sent) and chronologically thereunder.
  - To Moscow A.R.A. headquarters (Box 280)
    - General
      - (121-1113), 1921 September 24 -November 3 (Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 357
      - (1152-2762), 1921 November 3 -December 2 (Box 281, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 358
      - (2763-4502), 1921 December-1922 January (Box 282, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 359
      - 50-1439), 1922 January-February ( (Box 283, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 360
      - (1385-2499), 1922 February-March (Box 284, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 361
      - (2254-3025), 1922 March-April (Folder 2)
      - (3190-3858), 1922 May-June (Box 285, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 362
      - (3879-8936), 1922 June-July (Box 286, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 363
      - (4096-5344 and 9014-13724), 1922 July-October (Box 287, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 364
      - (5362-5595 and 42-1147), 1922 October (Folder 2)
      - (1292-4734), 1922 November-1923 January 4 (Box 288, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 365
      - (4737-8738), 1923 January 4 -March 31 (Box 289, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 366
      - (8754-13217), 1923 April 2 -July 11 (Box 290, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 367
      - (small number, household number), 1922 January-April (Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 291, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 368
  - From Moscow A.R.A. headquarters (Box 292)
    - (1-500), 1921 August 22 -December 6 (Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 369
    - (501-889), 1921 December 6-1922 February 8 (Box 293, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 370
    - (890-1250), 1922 February 8 -March 20 (Box 294, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 371
    - (1251-1655), 1922 March 21 -May 15 (Box 295, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 372
    - (1656-2000), 1922 May 16 -July 11 (Box 296, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 373
    - (2001-2571), 1922 July 11 -October 31 (Box 297, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 374
    - (2572-2900), 1922 November 1-24 (Box 298, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 375
    - (2901-3258), 1922 November 24 -December 30 (Box 299, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 376
    - (3258-3432), 1922 December 30-1923 January 30 (Box 300, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 377
    - (3433-3742), 1923 February 1 -March 31 (Folder 2)
    - (3743-4069), 1923 April 1 -May 31 (Box 301, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 378
    - (4070-4306), 1923 June 12 -July 19 (Folder 2)
- Washington Office, Subject File, 1921-1925
  Available on microfilm reels 379-432
  Reports, memoranda, correspondence, agreements, minutes of meetings, instructions, dispatches, telegrams, histories, notes, questionnaires, statistical data, maps, charts, rosters, press summaries, printed matter, and other records of the Washington office relating to Russian relief, arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Miscellaneous (Box 302)
    - A-Al (Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 379
    - Am-Aq (Folder 2)
    - Ar-Az (Folder 3)
    - Ba-Bam (Folder 4)
    - Ban-Bem (Folder 5)
    - Ben-Bi (Folder 6)
    - Bl-Bor (Folder 7)
    - Bos-Bri (Folder 8)
    - Bro-Buk (Folder 9)
    - Bul-Bz (Folder 10)
    - Ca-Cg (Box 303, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 380
    - Cha-Chz (Folder 2)
    - Ci-Cn (Folder 3)
    - Co-Com (Folder 4)
    - Con-Coz (Folder 5)
    - Cr-Cz (Folder 6)
    - Da (Folder 7)
    - De-Dn (Folder 8)
    - Do (Folder 9)
    - Dr-Dz (Box 304, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 381
    - Ea-Ef (Folder 2)
    - Eg-Eq (Folder 3)
    - Er-Ez (Folder 4)
    - Fa (Folder 5)
    - Fb-Fn (Folder 6)
    - Fo (Folder 7)
    - Fp-Fz (Folder 8)
    - Ga-Gd (Folder 9)
    - Ge-Gn (Folder 10)
    - Go (Box 305, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 382
    - Gp-Gz (Folder 2)
    - Ha-Hap (Folder 3)
    - Har-Haz (Folder 4)
    - He-Hh (Folder 5)
    - Hi (Folder 6)
    - Ho (Folder 7)
    - Hr-Hz (Folder 8)
    - Ia-Ir (Folder 9)
    - Is-Iz (Box 306, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 383
    - Ja-Jn (Folder 2)
    - Jo-Jz (Folder 3)
    - Ka (Folder 4)
    - Ke-Kk (Folder 5)
    - Kl-Ko (Folder 6)
    - Kp-Kz (Folder 7)
    - La (Folder 8)
    - Lb-Lh (Folder 9)
    - Li-Ln (Folder 10)
    - Lo-Lt (Folder 11)
    - Lu-Lz (Folder 12)
    - Ma-Man (Box 307, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 384
    - Mc (Folder 2)
    - Mar-Mb (Folder 3)
    - Me-Mim (Folder 4)
    - Min-Morp (Folder 5)
    - Morr-Mz (Folder 6)
    - Na-Net (Folder 7)
    - Neu-Nm (Folder 8)
    - Nn-Nz (Folder 9)
    - Oa-Ol (Folder 10)
    - Om-Oz (Box 308, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 385
    - Pa (Folder 2)
    - Pe (Folder 3)
    - Ph-Ln (Folder 4)
    - Po (Folder 5)
    - Pr-Pz (Folder 6)
    - Q (Folder 7)
    - Ra (Folder 8)
    - Rb-Rg (Folder 9)
    - Rh-Rn (Folder 10)
    - Ro-Rt (Folder 11)
    - Ru-Rz (Folder 12)
    - Sa-Sb (Box 309, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 386
    - Sc-Sg (Folder 2)
    - Sh (Folder 3)
    - Si-Sl (Folder 4)
    - Sm-Sn (Folder 5)
    - So-Sq (Folder 6)
    - Sr-St (Folder 7)
    - Su-Sz (Folder 8)
    - Ta-Tg (Folder 9)
    - Th-Tn (Folder 10)
    - To-Tr (Folder 11)
    - Ts-Tz (Box 310, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 387
    - U (Folder 2)
    - Va-Ve (Folder 3)
    - Vf-Vz (Folder 4)
    - Wa (Folder 5)
    - We-Wh (Folder 6)
    - Wi-Wn (Folder 7)
    - Wo-Wz (Folder 8)
    - Y (Folder 9)
    - Z (Folder 10)
  - Accounting (Box 311, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 388
  - Adult feeding (Folder 2)
  - Agreements
    - General (Folder 3)
    - Clothing (Folder 4)